A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #3406: R. Shapley (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - GP #3407: G. A. Langer, A. J. Brady, K. I. Shine, W. G. Sanborn (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - GP #3408: L. A. Beaug‚, Norma Adragnr (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - GP #3409: G. D. McCann (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - GP #3410: H. T. Meryman (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - GP #3411: Wei Young (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - GP #3412: G. L. Wright (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - GP #3413: Y. Ito, H. Kuriyama (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - GP #3414: N. Koyama, K. Kurihara (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - GP #3415: Gene A. Marrill (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - GP #3416: Ellen Rogus, Kenneth L. Zierler (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - GP #3417: Alan R. Freeman (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - GP #3418: P. Lipton, I. S. Edelman (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - GP #3419: R. Gunn, D. C. Toseteson (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - GP #3420: S. L. Kimzey, J. S. Willis (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - GP #3421: S. L. Kimzey, J. S. Willis (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - GP #3422: Phillip Kashin, William F. Danforth (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - GP #3423: Crandall, Klocke, Forster (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - GP #3424: Barnola, Camejo, Villegas (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - GP #3425: Kunze, Combes, Walker, Brown (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - GP #3246: Villegas, Sevick (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - GP #3427: Rapoport (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - GP #3428: Gary-B obo, A. K. Solomon (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - GP #3429: Hoffman, Tosteson (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - GP #3430: Croker, Trump (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - GP #3431: Cales, Majeau-Chargois (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - GP #3432: Mekata (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - GP #3433: Sha'afi, Hajjar (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - GP #3434: Connoly, Gaugh, Winegrad (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - GP #3435: D. H. Riddick, F. M. Kregenow, J. Orloff (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - GP #3436: Villegas, Villegas, DiPolo, Villegas (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - GP #3437: Goldsmith, Fernandez, Goldsmith (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - GP #3438: Thomas U. L. Biber (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - GP #3439: Thomas H. Maren (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - GP #3440: Rastogi, Shukla, Yadava (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - GP #3441: J. Farrant, A. E. Wollgar (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - GP #3442: Freeman (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - GP #3443: Ismail-Beigi, Elderman (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - GP #3444: J. T. Van Bruggen, Marija Janko, Bozidor Janko (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - GP #3445: Savitz, A. K. Solomon (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - GP #3446: Dunham, Hoffman (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - GP #3447: Philip A. Knouf, Aser Rothstein (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - GP #3448: Philip A. Knouf, Aser Rothstein (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - GP #3449: C. Y. Kao (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - GP #3450: Macklin, Josephson (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - GP #3451: R. I. Sha'afi, C. M. Gary-Bobo, A. K. Solomon (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - GP #3454: H. Kaike, H. Mack Brown, S. Hagiwara (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - GP #3453: Bruce W. Knight (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - GP #3454: A. M. Granada, S. Yazulla (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - GP #3455: Kregenow (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - GP #3456: Kregenow (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - GP #3457: J. A. Zadunaisky, M. A. Lande (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - GP #3458: M. B. Thorson, J. Thorson (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - GP #3459: Winegrad (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - GP #3460: Richard C. Rose, Stanley Schultz (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - GP #3461: Bownds, Gordon-Walker, Gaide-Huguenin, Robinson (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - GP #3462: G. R. Kepner, D. C. Tosteson (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - GP #3463: T. Narahashi, E. D. Albuquerque, T. Deguchi (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - GP #3464: Praissman, Miller, Berkowitz (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - GP #3465: Melvin Praissman, Irving F. Miller, Hary P. Gregor, Jesse M. Berkowitz (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - GP #3466: Offner (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - GP #3467: Thorpe, Seeman (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - GP #3468: L. Cedrini, A. Ferroni, D. Lavisolo (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - GP #3469: E. Neher (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - GP #3470: Srebro, Behbehane (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - GP #3471: Athenstaedt (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - GP #3472: Athenstaedt (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - GP #3473: Tarr, Trank (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - GP #3474: Manthey (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - GP #3475: Bittar, Tong, Chen, Danielson (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - GP #3476: Gordon, Fry, Barr (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - GP #3477: M. Chau-Wong, P. Seeman (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - GP #3478: J. E. Lisman, Joel E. Brown (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - GP #3479: Yoshiaki Nakamaru, Arnold Schwartz (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - GP #3480: Daniel, Paton (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - GP #3481: Philip I. Palimeni, Ernest Page (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - GP #3482: Racotta, Cirues (not a manuscript; a summary) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - GP #3483: Vizi, Illes, Ronai, Knoll (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - GP #3484: Guttman, Hachmeister (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - GP #3485: Guttman, Hachmeister (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - GP #3486: C. Y. Kao, J. R. McCullough, H. L. Davidson (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - GP #3487: Matsumoto, Naka (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - GP #3488: R. W. Berry, M. J. Cohen (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - GP #3489: Il Sup Kah (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - GP #3490: Lannergren (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - GP #3491: Ling, G. Bhor (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - GP #3492: Dawling, Ripps (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - GP #3493: Wang, Jhan (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - GP #3494: Anderson, Ramon, Snyder (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - GP #3495: Steinbach, Bennett (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - GP #3496: Stiles, Alexander (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - GP #3497: Pribor, Nara (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - GP #3498: U. Uinon (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - GP #3499: Costantin (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - GP #3500: Lindemann, Rikmenspoel (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - GP #3501: Alonso, Bazerque, Arrigo, Tumilasci (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - GP #3502: Broding, Tomita (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - GP #3503: Rothberg (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - GP #3504: Armstrong (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - GP #3505: Tarr (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - GP #3506: Robbins, Yonezawa (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - GP #3507: DeVoe (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - GP #3508: Villegas, Barnola (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - GP #3509: Srebro, Behehani (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - GP #3510: Rapuzzi (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - GP #3511: Laskowski, Thies (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - GP #3512: Bloomquist, Curtis, Twarog (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - GP #3513: Lipton (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - GP #3514: Mulieri, Sichel (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - GP #3515: Griffin, Szaro, Weltman (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - GP #3516: Hermsmeyer, Rulon, Sprelakis (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - GP #3517: Crawford, Hampton (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - GP #3518: Washio (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - GP #3519: MacKnight, Civan, Leaf (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - GP #3520: Chapman (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - GP #3521: Adams (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - GP #3522: Reuter, White, Wald (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - GP #3523: Gibbions, Fozzard (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - GP #3524: Arch (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - GP #3525: Gershfield, Muramatsu (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - GP #3526: McLaughlin, Szabo, Eisenman (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - GP #3527: Huddart (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - GP #3528: Spekreijse, Schllart (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - GP #3529: Chance, Rosini (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - GP #3530: Engel, Barcilon, Eisenberg (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - GP #3531: Strickholm (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - GP #3532: R. I. Sha?afi, E. Pascoe (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - GP #3533: French, Holdden, Stein (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - GP #3534: Harrington, Johnson (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - GP #3535: F. Mekata, H. Niu (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - GP #3536: Masahiro Ozeki (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - GP #3537: Jen-Shih Lee (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - GP #3538: Eisenberg, Costantin (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - GP #3539: dos Remedias, Millikan, Morales (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - GP #3540: Gamow, Johnson (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - GP #3541: Hiraoka, Hecht (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - GP #3542: Nolte, Brown (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - GP #3543: Nolte, Brown (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - GP #3544: Gaffey (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - GP #3545: Mathews (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - GP #3546: Abernethy (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - GP #3547: Hinkle, Van Der Kloot (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - GP #3548: Whittembury, Sullivan, Giebisch (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - GP #3549: Zelman (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - GP #3550: Rifkin (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - GP #3551: Hillie (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - GP #3552: Parisi, Piccinni (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - GP #3553: Wright, Brown, Wald (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - GP #3554: Uehara, Marita (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - GP #3555: Brandt, Reuben, Grundfest (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - GP #3556: Taylor, Preiser, Sandow (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - GP #3557: L. E. Moore (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - GP #3558: Schwartz, Rosen, Steinmetz (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - GP #3559: Foulks, Miller, Perry (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - GP #3560: Foulks, Miller, Perry (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - GP #3561: Seldin, White, Brown (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - GP #3562: Brown, White (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - GP #3563: Cochrane, Parsons (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - GP #3564: Gurtner (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - GP #3565: Weiner, Lee (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - GP #3566: Israel, MacDonald, Bernstein, Rosenmann (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - GP #3567: Cranefield, Wit, Hoffman (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - GP #3568: Venosa, Ruarte, Horowicz (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - GP #3569: Kavaler, Hyman, Lefkowitz (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - GP #3570: Bloomquist, Curtis (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - GP #3571: Guttman, Hachmeister (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - GP #3572: Danielson, Bittar Chen, Tong (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - GP #3573: Frizzell, Schultz (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - GP #3574: J. I. Korenbrat, R. A. Cone (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - GP #3575: I. Rapoport, M. Hari, I. Klatz (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - GP #3576: Tarr, Jurewicz (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - GP #3577: Geddes, Mailman (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - GP #3578: Lorkovic (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - GP #3579: Flock (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - GP #3580: Bailey, Ong, Queen (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - GP #3581: Eisenberg, Vaughan, Howell (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - GP #3582: Vaughn, Howell, Eisenberg (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - GP #3583: Cohen (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - GP #3584: Cohen, Hayashi (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - GP #3585: Danielson, Bittar, Chen, Tong (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - GP #3586: Deren, Rosen (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - GP #3587: Reddy, Hoing (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - GP #3588: Gur, Purple, Whitehead (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - GP #3589: Sherman, Atwood (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - GP #3590: Gutknecht, Bruner, Tosteson (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - GP #3591: Chambers (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - GP #3592: White, Thorson (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - GP #3593: gardner, Conlon (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - GP #3594: Brown (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - GP #3595: Lehman, Szent-Gyorgyi (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - GP #3596: Caputo (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - GP #3597: Caputo (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - GP #3598: Caputo (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - GP #3599: Christ, Nishi (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - GP #3600: McCann, Arnett (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - GP #3601: Harrington (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - GP #3602: Forman, Ford, Sonnenblick (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - GP #3603: Kawata, Chen (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - GP #3604: Hakim (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - GP #3605: Winegrad (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - GP #3606: Winegrad (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - GP #3607: Swihart (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - GP #3608: Naitoh, Eckert, and Friedman (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - GP #3609: Poznansky and Solomon (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - GP #3610: Fairbanks, Hoffert and Fromm (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - GP #3611: Martin (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - GP #3612: Murphy and Martin (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - GP #3613: Murphy and Martin (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - GP #3614: Murphy and Martin (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - GP #3615: Eggena (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - GP #3616: Eagle, Bronk Introduction (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - GP #3617: Armstrong and Hillie (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - GP #3618: Romualdez, Sha'afi, Lange and Solomon (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - GP #3619: Mandel and Curran (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - GP #3620: Kregenow (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - GP #3621: Wittenberg and Haedrich (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - GP #3622: Miyamoto, M. and Hubbard, John I. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - GP #3623: Ahlquist and Gamow (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - GP #3624: Spring and Paganelli (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - GP #3625: Novotny and Bianchi (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - GP #3626: Lisman and Brown (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - GP #3627: Brown and Lisman (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - GP #3628: Carsten (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - GP #3629: Goldman, L. and Schauf, C.L. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - GP #3630: Rogus and Zierler (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - GP #3631: Rogus and Zierler (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - GP #3632: Rogus and Zierler (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - GP #3633: Fishman, Ehrenstein and Oosting (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - GP #3634: Trubatch (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - GP #3635: Hamman and Seliger (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - GP #3636: Athenstaedt (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - GP #3637: Nelson, Peacock, and Minna (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - GP #3638: Carter and Rector (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - GP #3639: Suarez, Kurtz et. Al. (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - GP #3640: Ramon, Anderson and Moore (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - GP #3641: A. Esbin (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - GP #3642: Schultz (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - GP #3643: Hillie (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - GP #3644: Bianchi and Bolton (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - GP #3645: Parisi, Reader and DeRoberts (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - GP #3646: Repke and Katz (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - GP #3647: Latore, Ehrenstein and Lecar (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - GP #3648: Knight (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - GP #3649: Wiederhold, Macnichol and Bell (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - GP #3650: Macnichol (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - GP #3651: Chappell and Dowling (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - GP #3652: Dowling and Chappell (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - GP #3653: Srebro and Behbehani (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - GP #3654: Srebro and Behbehani (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - GP #3655: Sperelakis and Shigenobu (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - GP #3656: Dipolo (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - GP #3657: Millman and Omachi (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - GP #3658: Briden and Alpert (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - GP #3659: Gardner and Frantz (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - GP #3660: Gardner (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - GP #3661: Chertok and Lake (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - GP #3662: Audesirk (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - GP #3663: Onishi, Mike, Kanekoy and Tonomura (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - GP #3664: Uyamamoto (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - GP #3665: Magaribuchi, Ito and Kuriyama (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - GP #3666: Magaribuchi, Ito and Kuriyama (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - GP #3667: Somlyo (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - GP #3668: Arch (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - GP #3669: Linder (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - GP #3670: Deno (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - GP #3671: Snipes and Lengemann (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - GP #3672: Muller and Finkelstein (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - GP #3673: Muller and Finkelstein (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - GP #3674: Kregenow and Hoffman (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - GP #3675: Pollack and Lampen (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - GP #3676: Pollack and Lampen (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - GP #3677: Fletcher (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - GP #3678: Hartzell and Fambrough (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - GP #3679: Parlow, Ross, Motwani and McDougal (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - GP #3680: Sevcik and Narahashi (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - GP #3681: Pooler (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - GP #3682: Pooler (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - GP #3683: Glantz (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - GP #3684: Russell and Brown (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - GP #3685: Russell and Brown (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - GP #3686: Miethe (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - GP #3687: Obara and Bennett (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - GP #3688: Bezanilla and Armstrong (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - GP #3689: Garcia-Romeu and Ehrenfeld (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - GP #3690: Solaro and Briggs (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - GP #3691: Protela, Perez, Vaccari, Stewart and Dowben (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - GP #3692: Hillman, Dodge, Hochstein, Knight and Minke (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - GP #3693: Minke, Hochstein, and Hillman (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - GP #3694: Hochstein, Minke and Hillman (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - GP #3695: Cedar, Kandel and Schwartz (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - GP #3696: Cedar and Schwartz (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - GP #3697: Baskin, Sabbadini, L.M. Davis (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - GP #3698: Sjodin and Beauge (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - GP #3699: Kawai, Mauro and Grundfest (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - GP #3700: Goldrich (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - GP #3701: Borle (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - GP #3702: McDonald and DeHaan (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - GP #3703: Bozler (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - GP #3704: Mller- Mohnssen and Barske (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - GP #3705: Bernard and Jard (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - GP #3706: Stephenson (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - GP #3707: Frank, Cavanagh and Kenyon (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - GP #3708: Frank and Cavanagh (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - GP #3709: Eggena (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - GP #3710: Tahara, Kimizuka and Koketsu (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - GP #3711: Penefsky (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - GP #3712: Rikmenspoel, Jacklet, Oris, Lindeman (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - GP #3713: Adolph and Juan (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - GP #3714: Gage and McBurney (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - GP #3715: McArdle and Albuquerque (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - GP #3716: April and Brandt (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - GP #3717: Ripochet, Bourquet and Parisi (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - GP #3718: Bourquet, Ripochet and Parisi (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - GP #3719: Dowling and Ripps (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - GP #3720: Chirandini and Stefani (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - GP #3721: Hajjar, Khuri and Curran (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - GP #3722: Y. Palti, W.J. Adelman and J.P. Senft (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - GP #3723: Komor, Loos and Tanner (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - GP #3724: Mobley, Freygang, and Gunn (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - GP #3725: P.R. Miles and J.W. Woodbury (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - GP #3726: Scarpa, Baldassare and Inesi (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - GP #3727: Rich and Brady (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - GP #3728: Alkon and Fuortes (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - GP #3729: Tawada and Miyamoto (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - GP #3730: Kung-ming Jan and Shu Chien (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - GP #3731: Kung-ming Jan and Shu Chien (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - GP #3732: Yue, Davis and Hassanein (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - GP #3733: Wooten and Wald (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - GP #3734: Fein and Devoe (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - GP #3735: Parker (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - GP #3736: Strichartz (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - GP #3737: Andreoli and Watkins (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - GP #3738: Lannergren and Noth (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - GP #3739: Rall and Schottelius (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - GP #3740: Freygang and Gunn (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - GP #3741: Uehara (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - GP #3742: Rapoport and Bidinger (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - GP #3743: Jacobsen (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - GP #3744: Gliozzi, Penco, Battezzati and Ciferri (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - GP #3745: Washio (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - GP #3746: Ehrlich, Benech, Franchi and Yanez (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - GP #3747: Naitoh and Eckert (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - GP #3748: Alkon and Bak (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - GP #3749: Gunn, Dalmark, Tosteson and Wieth (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - GP #3750: Machemer and Eckert (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - GP #3751: Frank (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - GP #3752: Twarog, Dewey and Hidaka (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - GP #3753: Goldman and Schauf (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - GP #3754: Kirby, Lindley, and Picken (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - GP #3755: Lindley, Kirby, Stuesse and Picken (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - GP #3756: Rose, Gelarden and Nahrwold (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - GP #3757: Godt (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - GP #3758: Ramlau (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - GP #3759: Nehr and Lux (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - GP #3760: Woodhull (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - GP #3761: McDonald, Sachs, and De Haan (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - GP #3762: Pour-Hassani, Klahr and Bricker (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - GP #3763: Pour-Hassani, and Klahr (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - GP #3764: Yeandle and Spiegler (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - GP #3765: Barchi (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - GP #3766: Ismail-Beigi, Salibian, Kirsten, and Edelman (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - GP #3767: Ismail-Beigi, Sampson, and Edelman (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - GP #3768: Biber and Sanders (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - GP #3769 rev. A: Sachs et.al. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - GP #3769: Ellory, Sachs, Dunham, Kropp, and Hoffman (Joseph) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - GP #3769 rev. B: Sachs et.al. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - GP #3770: Burkhardt and Whittle (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - GP #3771: Mounier (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - GP #3772: Robblee, Shepro, and Belamarich (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - GP #3773: Witkovsky, Nelson and Ripps (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - GP #3774: Sachs (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - GP #3775: Kitasato (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - GP #3776: Constantin and Taylor (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - GP #3777: Lisman and Brown (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - GP #3778: Lisman and Brown (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - GP #3779: Dambach (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - GP #3780: Stanton (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - GP #3781: Candia and Chiarandini (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - GP #3782: Wiitanen (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - GP #3783: Monster, Tamai and McHenry (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - GP #3784: Tarr and Trank (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - GP #3785: Alarie, Wakisaka and Oka (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - GP #3786: Sacchi and Perri (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - GP #3787: Washio (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - GP #3788: Sperelakis, Valle, Orozco, Martinez-Palomo and Rubio (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - GP #3789: Alkon (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - GP #3790: Sarboluki, Mohammad N. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - GP #3791: R.I. Sha'afi and E. Pascoe (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - GP #3792: Mayeri, Earl (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - GP #3793: Mayeri, Earl (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - GP #3794: Nelson, Philip G. and Peacock, John H. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - GP #3795: W.R. Galey, J.D. Owen and A.K. Solomon (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - GP #3796: Davis, Kenneth and Meier, Albert H. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - GP #3797: Mandel, Lazaro J. and Curran, Peter F. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - GP #3798: Adolph, Alan R. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - GP #3799: Richard S. Norman (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - GP #3800: Atwood and Lang (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - GP #3801: Bentzel (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - GP #3802: Bentzel, Spring, Hare and Paganelli (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - GP #3803: Mesibox, Ordal and Adler (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - GP #3804 (3803 rev.): Ordal and Adler (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - GP #3805: Anagnostopoulos (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - GP #3806: Wissner (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - GP #3807: Eggena (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - GP #3808: Fraser and Carlson (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - GP #3809: Hille (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - GP #3810: Batra and Edman (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - GP #3811: Davison (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - GP #3812: Alkon (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - GP #3813: Reisen and Ling (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - GP #3814: Blaustein, M.P. and Russell, J.M. (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - GP #3815: Armstrong, Bezanilla and Rojas (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - GP #3816: Hidaka, Twarog and Yamaguchi (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - GP #3817: Nelson, Colonomos, and McQuarrie (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - GP #3818: Kita and Van Der Kloot (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - GP #3819: Swanson and Solomon (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - GP #3820: Aronson and Cranefield (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - GP #3821: Mekata (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - GP #3822: Pace and Price (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - GP #3823: Homsher, Mommaerts, and Ricchiuti (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - GP #3823 (rev. A): Homsher and Rall (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - GP #3823 (rev. B): Homsher, Mommaerts, Ricchuiti (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - GP #3824: Hollins and Alpern (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - GP #3825: Winegrad (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - GP #3826: Norman and Werblin (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - GP #3827: Werblin (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - GP #3828: Werblin and Copenhagen (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - GP #3829: Anderson and Rescigno (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - GP #3830: Gibbs and Chapman (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - GP #3831: Uchitel and Garcia (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - GP #3832: Kleinzeller and McAvoy (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - GP #3833: Wilson (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - GP #3834: Knight and Welt (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - GP #3835: Mazur, Leibo and Miller (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - GP #3836: Mazur, Peter, Miller, R.H. and Leibo, S.P. (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - GP #3837: Caille and Hinke (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - GP #3838: Klee and Plonsey (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - GP #3839: Steinbach, Harris, Patrick, Schubert and Heinemann (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - GP #3840: Daw and Pearlman (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - GP #3841: Verniory, Lambert et. Al. (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - GP #3842: Foster and Lipson (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - GP #3843: Knauf, Proverbio and Hoffman (Box 37, Folder 28)